[{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734974904211,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":16550,"timeElapsed":50953},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734974908995,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":4783,"timeElapsed":55737},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734974913313,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":4317,"timeElapsed":60055},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734974916199,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2884,"timeElapsed":62940},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734974919219,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":3019,"timeElapsed":65961},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734974925966,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":6746,"timeElapsed":72708},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734974929044,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3078,"timeElapsed":75786},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734974938653,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":9608,"timeElapsed":85395},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734974940947,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":2293,"timeElapsed":87689},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734974953319,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":11098,"timeElapsed":100061},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734974955686,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2365,"timeElapsed":102428},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734974957925,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":2239,"timeElapsed":104667},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734974960299,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":2373,"timeElapsed":107041},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734974962468,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2168,"timeElapsed":109210},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734974970517,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":8048,"timeElapsed":117259},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734974972709,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2191,"timeElapsed":119451},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734974975625,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2914,"timeElapsed":122367},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734974978193,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2568,"timeElapsed":124935},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734974996125,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":16917,"timeElapsed":142867},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734974998544,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":2419,"timeElapsed":145286},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975002155,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3610,"timeElapsed":148897},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975005770,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3614,"timeElapsed":152512},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975008367,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":2596,"timeElapsed":155109},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975011914,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":3547,"timeElapsed":158656},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975015687,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":3772,"timeElapsed":162429},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975019456,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":3768,"timeElapsed":166198},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975022549,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":3092,"timeElapsed":169291},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975027453,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4904,"timeElapsed":174195},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975040299,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":11749,"timeElapsed":187041},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975042206,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":1907,"timeElapsed":188948},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975048056,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":5849,"timeElapsed":194798},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975053254,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":5197,"timeElapsed":199996},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975055282,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":2027,"timeElapsed":202024},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975058673,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":3391,"timeElapsed":205415},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975060653,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":1979,"timeElapsed":207395},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975062532,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":1879,"timeElapsed":209274},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975064606,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2073,"timeElapsed":211348},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975078622,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":12242,"timeElapsed":225364},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975081282,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":2660,"timeElapsed":228024},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975087977,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":6693,"timeElapsed":234719},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975090272,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":2295,"timeElapsed":237014},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975092184,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":1911,"timeElapsed":238926},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975094956,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":2771,"timeElapsed":241698},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975096883,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":1926,"timeElapsed":243625},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975100481,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":3597,"timeElapsed":247223},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975102256,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":1774,"timeElapsed":248998},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975117524,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":14251,"timeElapsed":264266},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975120072,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":2548,"timeElapsed":266814},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975122907,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":2834,"timeElapsed":269649},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975125593,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":2686,"timeElapsed":272335},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975127491,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":1897,"timeElapsed":274233},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975131719,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":4227,"timeElapsed":278461},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975133759,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":2039,"timeElapsed":280501},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975136814,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":3054,"timeElapsed":283556},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975138539,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":1724,"timeElapsed":285281},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975149666,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":10160,"timeElapsed":296408},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975152115,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":2448,"timeElapsed":298857},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975156354,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":4239,"timeElapsed":303096},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975159754,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3399,"timeElapsed":306496},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975163844,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":4090,"timeElapsed":310586},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975166071,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":2226,"timeElapsed":312813},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975167995,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":1923,"timeElapsed":314737},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975171207,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":3211,"timeElapsed":317949},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975173158,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":1950,"timeElapsed":319900},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975203727,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":29693,"timeElapsed":350469},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975205854,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2126,"timeElapsed":352596},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975207603,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1748,"timeElapsed":354345},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975209688,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2085,"timeElapsed":356430},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975212729,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3040,"timeElapsed":359471},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975217720,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":4991,"timeElapsed":364462},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975219681,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":1960,"timeElapsed":366423},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975222291,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":2609,"timeElapsed":369033},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975224283,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":1992,"timeElapsed":371025},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975233050,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":7834,"timeElapsed":379792},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975234826,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":1776,"timeElapsed":381568},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975236479,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":1652,"timeElapsed":383221},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975239051,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2571,"timeElapsed":385792},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975241241,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":2189,"timeElapsed":387983},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975244494,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":3252,"timeElapsed":391236},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975246169,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":1675,"timeElapsed":392911},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975248936,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2766,"timeElapsed":395678},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975252831,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":3894,"timeElapsed":399573},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975254862,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":2031,"timeElapsed":401604},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975260797,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":5223,"timeElapsed":407539},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975262245,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":1448,"timeElapsed":408987},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975264828,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":2582,"timeElapsed":411570},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975266819,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":1991,"timeElapsed":413561},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975269431,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":2611,"timeElapsed":416173},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975271699,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":2268,"timeElapsed":418441},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975274200,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":2500,"timeElapsed":420942},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975277043,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":2842,"timeElapsed":423785},{"subjectID":"ul08kxdwl1","prolificID":"674f49392a04ca838a809c9d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d7b2f2be23b113d71d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975278907,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":1863,"timeElapsed":425649}]